Double espresso, straight up.
One.
Hi, everyone.
It's like a half-a-year's sleep show with the girl trying to get all the coffees out.
Okay, where's my waitress?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
No foam.
Skim milk, I like.
Whip and bean.
Double.
Old school.
Cusack.
Tea, right here.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
Okay, there's the tea.
All right.
Chocolate.
And yours.
Thank you.
Whoa.
Hi.
You did not just do that.
What can I get you?
Uh, thanks.
I've already been helped.
Great.
Next.
University of Miami?
Yeah.
I just don't see you trading in your flannels for flip flops.
I don't know.
Yeah, you've got a lot of flops.
Well, I figure if you got a chance to start over, why not start over where there's a beach?
I am feeling a bit guilty leaving my parents to run the farm without me.
Yeah, I guess it would be really hard to replace, given all your skills and everything.
Skills?
Um, Lois, hey, can I get a double cappuccino?
Yeah, just a sec.
Oh, my God.
We've just been robbed.
Hi, Rooster.
You okay?
Clark? Clark?
What happened?
It was Clark.
Somebody save me.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
Just stay.
I've made this whole world.
I've done it for you.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
Just stay.
It must be kind of weird seeing the house you grew up in for the first time.
Do you recognize anything?
I mean the house or the cows?
The tractor? Anything?
You sure this is where I live?
Yeah.
You spend most of your time over there?
In a barn.
Well, normal was never really your style, Clark.
That was my attempt at humor.
Sometimes I crash and burn, sorry.
If you've ever been to your native town, you know that Landisilt is one of the best.
You gonna see what some people do?
It's the SEÑOR'S place.
I like the way it's more formal, sourness.
Clark took it,
It's your house.
It was stuck.
Actually, I think it was locked.
Mr. Kent.
Mrs. Kent.
What the hell happened to the door?
You know, I tried to open it, and then...
Yeah, and then some freak wind came and just blew it right off.
Right.
So, Lois, do you know where the Kents are?
They're in Metropolis for Mr. Kent's heart exam.
Clark, you know that.
Well, not so much.
He has amnesia, and he's having a hard time...
Again?
What do you mean, again?
Well, at least this time you got clothes on.
Lois, we need to get his parents back home.
Well, that's going to be a little hard.
Mr. Kent...
Mr. Kent has a one-way ticket on the Ambien Express.
He's going to be out of commission for a couple of days.
So, what happened?
Well, the last thing I remember, I woke up in the alley,
and I was with...
Chloe.
I'm thinking he caught up to whoever was behind the robbery
and plain sight incident.
And what, we have a thief with memory repo?
I guess that could explain why in some weird small village in way
I zoned out eight coffee orders before I found the till was empty.
I'm going to go to the torch and see what I can find.
It would be hard to find an ingredient without having an amnesia.
Yeah, just leave Mr. Memory Reboot to me.
I'm getting to be a pro at this.
But you know what, you're going to have to put up with PB&J
because that's the extent of my culinary skills.
Okay?
Duh, please tell me I'm not related to her.
No, I am.
You live with her.
Clark!
You know what?
I'm going to take him up to the barn.
See if anything up there jogs his memory.
All right.
See you.
Bye.
yourself? We need to talk. What's with the Cheshire cat routine? A little something from
central Kansas. Congratulations. I think if they were going to object to you, they probably
wouldn't have sent you a novella. No, probably not. Hey, I was thinking that we could go
check out the dorms on campus this weekend. Jason, I'm not sure that I'm going to go to
central Kansas. I'm not even sure if I'm going to go to college at all. I'm actually
giving this a lot of thought. Which part? The part that we've been planning this for
an entire year? Well, I thought this was our one chance to put everything that's happened
over the past couple months behind us. It could be like Paris all over again. Yeah.
Jason, last summer was incredible.
But we have to face it. We haven't been able to recreate that here. Not with everything
that's happened. Not with the stones or your mom and all of the lies. How long have you
known? I mean, your feelings don't just change overnight, so you've obviously been thinking
about this a while. Yeah. Yeah. Ever since this turned into the same relationship I was
trying to leave behind when I went to Paris. Oh, so this is about Clark? No, it's not about
Clark. Jason, it's about us.
Leave me alone, impartial little brother. Maybe I should leave my old self alone.
No. Leave her alone. I'm not in a relationship with you. And you're not even thinking about
me. No. I thought this was about us holding it.
No, it's about hate. I'm not comfy with you. You gave yourself up to the big shot.
We did this because of you. Get used to it. It's not about being approached collar to
I've turned into.
What are you talking about?
Just don't give up on me.
Jesus.
OK?
You have no idea how much I've been protecting you.
Do you?
Here.
Bend this.
This is metal.
I can't bend this.
Just like you can't pull a door off its hinges, right?
Try it.
OK.
How did I do that?
Why did I always picture myself on the other end of this
conversation?
Um, here.
Come here.
Sit.
Smallville was hit with the world's
meteor shower when you were little.
Now I know this sounds way out there,
but some of the meteor rocks have had
an extraterrestrial effect on certain people in the town.
And it's my theory that you are one of them.
Extraterrestrial powers?
You mean I'm some sort of alien?
No, of course not.
Mutant?
Yeah.
Who has saved my life on more than one occasion?
See, you've sort of taken it upon yourself
to be Smallville's self-appointed hero.
And if you ask me, I think that that is amazing.
Well, we must have been pretty good friends
if I trusted you with all this.
Yeah, well, actually, you didn't.
It's okay.
I mean, you were just protecting yourself.
A lot of people would betray you if they knew.
But you wouldn't, would you?
Never.
It would be excepted.
I don't think about bothering peopleão
Chief, please do me a favor,
could you just ugly wasg plant
yet just blow over these fireад
because I omega thw maண hands?
Porque defining el cerebro en Liz Tawohor.
That's what he wants.
Seriously?
Chloe, is there something there?
Back behind, near your feet, under the mat.
Okay, how'd you know that was there?
Well, I could... I guess...
I can see through things.
Hold on a minute.
Are you telling me that you can see through solid objects?
I guess that's one you didn't know about, huh?
No.
And that might be one of those abilities you're gonna want to keep a lid on.
You know, I've been thinking about that.
You know, I don't know why I was worried so much about what people think.
I don't know why I let it rule my life.
I mean, you understood.
Yeah, but, Clark, unfortunately,
some people in Smallville aren't as progressive as your post-Dermatitis tour guide.
Yeah, but that should be their problem, not mine.
Look, I understand how eager you are
to throw an impromptu...
coming-out party.
I mean, I've only spent the last couple of hours
blocking for the man behind the mask,
and it's not as easy as I thought it would be.
But please just sleep on it.
I know. It's just...
I mean, how can anyone ever get to know me
if I'm never myself?
I know. It's hard.
But I imagine that if you didn't tell people,
you must have had a lifetime of reasons for not doing it.
So that's why we need to get your memory back.
So I can do what?
Get back to lying to everyone?
Clark.
Chloe, I'm not sure I want that.
I don't want that.
At least wait until you can talk to your parents, okay?
Clark?
Lewis?
Ah!
Premature combustion.
That's one I didn't need to know about.
Who is that?
That?
Is Lana Lang.
Love of your life.
Looks like one more thing you don't remember.
You usually hide all those emotions.
I came to ask if you were doing okay.
But,
looks like I got my answer.
My love,
my life is a complete void.
How would you feel?
Oh, pity party.
These are fun.
Look, Chloe's very protective of me.
I guess there's a lot of people that I can't trust.
And you can't tell who they are.
Look, you may not remember all the players on the board,
but you can still play the game.
You can tell me how I'm supposed to do that?
Trust your gut.
Just you.
OK.
You tell me how you feel.
I just learn it every time.
It's funny.
Always Daddy said his fault.
Thinking about what would I do with you,
if I someday fell for you,
would I be a good son to you,
with no cookouts.
No, Margaret.
Not a step from you.
pratique what the real thing was.
So,
what about 입 fleecing life?
Tell me what you wanna do,
if you need any help selling stuff I can.
You know I'd love to help.
And maybe we'll make funds.
Come on,
don't worry about me.
Don't worry about me.
One more kiss could be the best thing
One more lie could be the worst
In my head there's only you now
This world falls on me
In this world
Hi, Clark.
Hi.
I heard about what happened to you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I suppose you don't even know who I am.
Lana.
I was gonna come by later.
I didn't think I'd see you here.
I actually came here to see you.
Chloe, she...
She told me that we used to...
Yeah.
Yeah, we did.
What happened?
I mean, please, I just...
I'd really like to know.
So would I.
Who's me?
I don't understand.
If I felt anywhere near like I feel now...
Don't tell me.
I don't want to know.
I don't want to know because this time...
It'll be different.
This time...
Um...
I don't think we should talk about this right now.
When can we talk about this?
I don't know.
How did he get here?
Looks like the heart remembers more than the brain.
Come on, cuz.
Don't give one more second of thought to those vacant...
You baby Bloos.
Hey, good news.
We traced that daypass we found to
Grand View motor cross park.
He lives in Smallville, so we thought we'd go check out the address.
Coming?
Kevin?
What are you doing here?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Look, I'm sorry, Dad, but I couldn't stay there any longer.
Kev, you have to go back.
You're in the middle of your treatment.
It's not working.
Look, I know you want to keep what I did to Dylan a secret,
but no matter what they do to try to make me forget it,
I'll always know the truth.
Kev.
Don't worry about me.
Okay, I've got money together.
I'll be fine.
After what I did, I can't expect you to look at me every day.
Kevin, please let us help you.
You can't.
That's not what I meant.
That place turned me into some kind of freak.
What do you mean?
This.
Yes?
Hi.
I'm here to collect on a little spontaneous line of credit
your son decided to take out with the Talon,
along with two minutes of my memory.
Oh, yeah, you must be mistaken.
Actually, Mr. Grady, we found this by the register at the Talon.
It's Kevin's.
We just want to talk to him.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
My son is out of town at the moment.
And by out of town, I'm guessing you're meaning
undergoing some kind of treatment at Summerholt Institute.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help but notice the parking pass on your windshield.
I believe that's nobody's business but ours.
Excuse me.
Look, we're not saying he did it.
We just need to find out what he knows.
All right.
Yes, my son is a patient at Summerholt.
Last fall I took both my boys hunting,
uh, archery clearing.
There was an accident.
Kevin was loading his gun and uh,
I lost my son, Dylan.
Mr. Gray, I'm sorry.
Kevin couldn't live with himself.
He was, uh...
And I didn't know which way to turn.
So I...
Well, we thought that if Summer Holt
could help erase those memories,
well, then maybe Kevin could get on with his life.
Excuse me.
I need to try and find my son.
Thank you.
Look, it tugs at the heartstrings,
but I'm not sure I totally buy it.
I'm gonna go have a look around.
Clark, are you okay?
I can hear someone running.
What?
And the Super Weedies' abilities just keep coming.
Where are they?
They're on the side of the house.
Well, go get them.
It sounds like he's on a motorcycle now.
Trust me on this one, Clark. Run.
Chloe.
Just run, Clark!
Clark!
I guess the whole castle thing
didn't take off in the neighborhood.
I'm friends with a billionaire.
Funny.
You never seen that in press before.
Mr. Luther?
Lex, I'm guessing you don't remember it,
but we kind of dropped the formalities the day I ran you off a bridge.
Look, as much as I'm sure we're all enjoying this little icebreaker,
we did come here for a reason.
I was hoping that you still had your contact at the Summerholt Institute.
Chloe mentioned that they had done some experiments on you.
Yeah, we were guessing that the guy that did this to Clark
is undergoing some sort of treatment to have his memory wiped.
Probably not too far of a leap,
given there are unnerving advancements in the field.
Look, I'll make a few calls, see what I can find.
Chloe, if you don't mind, I'd like to have a word with Clark.
Well, I promised his parents that I would get him home.
Well, I think I can manage that.
It's all right, Chloe, you could use a break from chaperone duty.
I'll be okay.
Okay.
Clark, be careful.
Clark, I think I might know something that could jog your memory.
Okay.
I found these keys.
And ever since, the two of us have been working together,
trying to solve its mysteries.
That's just between you and me.
What do all these symbols mean?
I know it'll probably sound strange,
but we think they're about you.
You.
Wait.
There should be a two-headed monster over here.
Then you remember this place.
No, I recognize it from the drawings in the loft.
We were, uh, documenting them.
Wait.
This wall shouldn't be here.
What do you mean?
Well, in the drawings, it shows a room behind this wall.
Clark, maybe we should head back to the loft
and take a closer look at the pictures.
I can help explain them to you.
I should probably get back.
I don't want my parents to worry.
Of course.
We're gonna have to clean up later.
You're gonna have 2 minutes.
Don't stress yourself.
Wait.
I don't know where Clark is.
What?
Well, when.
When?
Myже carefully packing for the trip!
It's their downhill way to the ile.
Thanks for the tip.
See ya later.
I just wanted to go over it.
Search for more targets.
Something a better look at.
You should definitely check in tonight.
You gotta make certain that Clark will be here soon.
Neither of you is doing well,
And you still can't fire him.
Motions it is at a friendly time
means you're out of business.
You don't have to do it,
nurse.
I'm sorry.
And where are you going to find him?
Where his brother died seems like a pretty good place to start.
Wait a minute.
Didn't his dad say that the accident happened at...
Outdoor Clearing?
Clark?
Kevin.
No, it's okay.
Listen, I came here to talk to you about Summerhold.
You're the guy from the talent.
How do you remember me?
I don't.
Whatever you did to me erased all my memories.
All of them?
With everyone else, it just wiped out the last few minutes.
I guess I'm not like everyone else.
Look, Kevin, I know it's going to be hard,
but I need to talk to you about the accident.
Is this where it happened?
Somewhere here.
Look.
I know.
It was somewhere here.
Just tell me what happened that day.
Okay.
Look, do you have any real memories from that day?
Kevin, what is it?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I've been trying to block the memories out.
Or maybe someone has already blocked them out for you.
No.
No, I was loading my gun.
It was right here.
But do you actually remember that?
Do you remember loading your gun
or do you remember someone telling you that?
No.
I didn't do it.
It was my dad.
How could he do that to me?
No.
I'm sorry, Kevin.
I don't get it.
I robbed the talent and I 86ed your memory.
I mean, why would you go through all this trouble for me?
I guess I just know what it's like to lose a part of your life.
I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do for you.
I mean, our only chance is to break into Summerhold,
but there's no way I can get you in there.
Maybe I can.
Look, this guy's kid robbed me,
then plucked the last forget-me-not pedal from my friend's brain.
You will let me back there, and you can do it with or without handcuffs.
Like I said, if you would sign in, I'll let someone know that you're here.
What part of this isn't getting through to you?
The last time I spoke to my cousin, she was here,
and I'm sure the psycho is holding her back there somewhere.
Ms. Lane.
Maybe they pay you enough to be rude,
but I doubt they pay you enough to do time in a county jail.
Oh.
Wait, wasn't it locked?
I think it was broken.
I don't know.
We should be able to reach the main office from down here.
Clark.
Clark, are you okay?
Okay.
You go ahead, I'll catch up.
I'll catch up with you.
Okay.
I wish I could erase your memories from just the last three days,
but I'm afraid I can't take that chance.
I'm gonna have to go back much further than that.
Mr. Grady, please don't do that.
Think of it as a gift.
Do you realize how many experiences in life
would be so much less painful
if we didn't have the memories to haunt us?
Dad!
Were you just gonna lie to me my whole life?
Huh?
To make me think I killed my own brother?
Kevin, calm down.
You're obviously having a psychological reaction to your treatment.
No one regrets what happened more than I do.
Ugh!
Uh-oh!
Oh!
Ugh!
Uh!
Clawing.
Wow.
Dear God in heaven.
Oh.
Lois? Sheriff?
Guess I shouldn't call you Smallville anymore.
I'm sorry.
Clark, what are you doing?
Are you just gonna stand there all day, or are you gonna untie her?
Hi.
Thanks.
Oh.
Here you go.
You say, how did you come across those tapes, Miss Sullivan?
Hey.
Did you ever hear that kid from the alley?
I've seen him before.
He's a nice guy.
I wants to go.
Even your girls?
I tried to pull you out of your car.
And that's the last thing I remember before what just happened in the lab.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that again, Clark. That was kind of my fault.
Well, I don't know what you did back there or why.
I get the feeling I owe you one.
I'd like to see it as more of an hour-even situation.
Something tells me I shouldn't stop you from leaving.
It's better if people don't ask too many questions about me.
Thanks for the chance at a clean slate, Clark.
Clark.
I was just looking for you.
Congratulations. I heard you got full retrieval.
Everything.
Everything except the last 24 hours.
Well, you didn't miss much, but I wanted to come in person to see the old Clark back.
Lex.
Chloe said she left me at the mansion because you wanted to talk.
What is it you wanted to talk about?
I just told you...
I told you about my own memory loss.
I thought it might be comforting.
I'm lucky to have so many good friends watching out for me.
Nothing you wouldn't have done for me, Clark.
I'm sure you will.
It was all for you.
Wemes, come on!
aggered.
How's the night?
She went out having dinner with me and...
Oh, episode two!
I was talking to Eric.
Yeah, you can stop calling him whenever you want.
I think everything's going well now.
How is cô,号?
doomless.
also saysитьсяピ convenient, and thought badly awkward.
Same as a man up in a car he loved.
Yesterday is a promise that you've broken.
Don't close your eyes.
This is your life.
Hi, I'm Marlee.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm just a little nervous.
What are you nervous about?
Don't close your eyes.
Were we supposed to do something?
Lana, I'm sorry.
I don't remember anything from the last day.
Are you going to stay?
Oh.
But everything else you remember now.
This is your life.
It's probably for the best.
Are you going to stay?
Were our plans like date kind of plans?
I'm nervous.
Because what about Jason?
Clark, you just wanted to talk.
There's nothing that can't wait till later.
Lana, wait.
I can't do this.
I can't let you walk out, not again.
It's OK.
We both know better than this.
I know.
That's why this time will be different.
This time?
Don't close your eyes.
This is your life.
And today is all you got now.
And.
And today is all you'll ever have.
Don't close your eyes.
This is your life.
Are you calling?
It's funny.
It's not hilarious, but it's funny.
My parents told me that you, Clark, sat and you called them home from Metropolis.
I'm sorry.
I want to say thanks.
Well, you could still use some help with your comedy routine, but it's not like I taught
you to eat solid foods again.
Still.
You're welcome.
So, it must have been kind of strange to have a zombie best friend walking around.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, I never really realized how complicated that zombie's life was.
Complicated?
Yeah.
Complicated.
Did I do something unusual?
You had a clean slate to start all over with,
and you made all the same choices.
Except for one.
Chloe, I need you to be completely honest with me.
Honest, huh?
What'd I do?
You trusted me.
I trusted você.
Eu tinha certeza.
Não sei o que te Peki do que eu estou fazendo,
mas who knows what I'm gonna do.
E leve o seu corpo às aldeias.
E vai ficar assim,
a partir do momento que você glorious.
Eu sinto que tenho savez você有 eu
Eu sinto que você sabe que eu teidei.
you